Guide to the Violet Hunt papers, 1858-1962.
Hunt, Violet papers, 1858-1962.
- Series IV. Manuscripts
  - 1. By Violet Hunt
    - a. Literary and General
      - "Packages under Stairs, 1st floor" -- [n.d.] (Box 25, Folder 13)
        ts. 3pp.
    - b. Howell Biography
      - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [Apr. 14, 1924-June 17, 1927] (Box 15, Folder 1-a-aa)
        Letters to her concerning the use of pictures for her biography of Charles Augustus Howell
        30 ll. + 7
        With folder, envelope, and five photographs of paintings.
        Letters from G.C. Williamson, Lord Barnard, C.W. Miller (sec'y to Lord Barnard), Theodore Cook, and T.G.C. Reynolds. Most are originals, although there are copies of two
      - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. (continued) -- [Apr. 14, 1924-June 17, 1927] (Box 15, Folder 1-a-aa)
        letters from Lord Barnard (of which there is also the original for one), a copy of a letter from G.C. Williamson, a copy of a letter from Theodore Cook to Major Fairfax- Blakesborough, and a draft of a letter from Violet Hunt to Lord Barnard.
      - Williamson, G. C. (George Charles), 1858-1942. -- [ca. 1919] (Box 15, Folder 2)
        [printed] Murray Marks and His Friends - [gatherings]
        36 ll.
        Includes pages 81-144, which contain part of a chapter on Charles Augustus Howell, about whom Violet Hunt was writing a biography.
      - Howell, Charles Augustus, 1839-1890. -- [ca. November 13, 1890] (Box 15, Folder 3)
        [printed] Catalogue of the Collection of Pictures, Objects of Art, and Decorative Furniture, of Charles A. Howell, Esq., Deceased,...
        24 ll. + 2
        With paper covers.
        Copy belonging to Rosa Corder, with "Miss R. Corder" written on the cover and with prices and names of buyers written next to each item.
      - Whistler, James McNeill, 1834-1903. -- [Sept. 18, 1878-July 14, 1882] (Box 15, Folder 4)
        TM & AM [Correspondence. Paddon Papers. The Owl and the Cabinet]
        45 ll. + 1
        Acquired by Violet Hunt for her biography of Charles Augustus Howell.
        Typed copy of a privately printed brochure, which consists of letters by James MacNeill Whistler, S. Wrefrod Paddon, J.E. McNay, F. Mewburn, Theo. Allingham, Sydney Morse, and W.A. Chapman, about the character and enterprises of Charles Augustus Howell.
      - Howell, Charles Augustus, 1839-1890. -- Sept. 25, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-a)
        TD [copy] [death certificate]
      - Howell, Charles Augustus, 1839-1890. (continued) -- Sept. 25, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-a)
        Certificate of his death on April 24, 1890.
      - Howell, Charles Augustus, 1839-1890. -- Oct. 9, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-b)
        TD [copy] [marriage certificate]
        Certificate of his marriage to Frances Kate Howell on August 21, 1867.
      - Howell, Rosalind Blanche, 1877- -- Jan. 4, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 5-c)
        TD [copy] [birth certificate]
        Rosalind Howell was born March 20, 1877.
        Rosalind Howell was the daughter of Charles Augustus and Frances Kate Howell.
      - Murray, Murray Howell, d. 1878 -- Oct. 6, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-d)
        Murray Howell Murray died August 1, 1878.
      - Howell, Catherine Emily, d. 1869 -- Oct. 6, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-e)
        Catherine Emily Howell died November 5, 1869.
      - Homan, Louisa Ann, d. 1879 -- Oct. 6, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-f)
        Louisa Ann Homan died April 21, 1879.
      - Homan, Jessica Ann Stewart, d. 1870 -- Oct. 6, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-g)
        Jessica Ann Stewart Homan died December 8, 1870.
      - Howell, Charles Augustus, 1839-1890. -- Oct. 6, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-h)
        AD [application for searching birth records]
      - Howell, Charles Augustus, 1839-1890. -- Oct. 6, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-h)
        Application made by Violet Hunt to obtain information for her biography of Charles Augustus Howell.
      - Howell, Frances Kate -- Oct. 6, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-i)
      - Murray, Murray Howell, d. 1878 -- Oct. 6, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5-j)
      - Howell, Charles Augustus, 1839-1890. -- 1889 (Box 15, Folder 6)
        [printed] Testimonials for Charles A. Howell, Esq.
        With paper cover and two newspaper clippings pasted inside back cover.
        Includes letters by Dante Gabriel Rossetti, William Michael Rossetti, Ford Madox Brown, John Everett Millais, Frederick Sandys, George Cruikshank, Thomas Woolner, Algernon Charles Swinburne, James MacNeill Whistler, Simeon Solomon, and others.
        Given to Violet Hunt by Emma Summers Gill.
      - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 15, Folder 7-a-w & 8-a-l)
        TM & AM [notes on Howell's later life]
        80 ll. + 114 + 1
        Housed in two folders.
        With original cover included in second folder.
        With T & ALS [draft] from Violet Hunt to Editor of Time & Tide, [n.d.], with another
      - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. (continued) -- [n.d.] (Box 15, Folder 7-a-w & 8-a-l)
        earlier draft and a sheet of comments by Ford [?] on verso of a manuscript page from Mr. Fleight [?].
        With personal recollections by Violet Hunt.
        With a review of David Larg's Trial by Virgins (by Peter Davies [?]).
        With TL [copy], Henry James to Violet Hunt, February 14, 1910.
      - Boyce, George Price, 1826-1897. -- [1865-1870] (Box 15, Folder 9-a-b)
        TM [copy] & AM [extracts from diary]
        27 ll. + envelope
        With front of folder with notes in Violet Hunt's hand.
        Violet Hunt transcription of Alice Street's copy of extracts concerning Charles Augustus Howell from the diary of her uncle, G.P. Boyce.
      - Howell, Charles Augustus, 1839-1890. -- [n.d.] (Box 15, Folder 10)
        TM [brief biography]
        Possibly written by Violet Hunt.
      - AM & TM [notes on Howell and the Dukes of Cleveland, with an article on the Dukes of Cleveland] -- 1928 (Box 15, Folder 11-a-w)
        83 ll. + 1
        With folder formerly enclosing these notes and other materials:
        With a brief biography of Charles Augustus Howell, attributed to G.C. Williamson
        ALS, Ethel Colburn Mayne to Violet Hunt, [n.d.]
        newspaper clipping concerning Howell and five newspaper clippings mentioning Violet Hunt's biography of Howell.
        On verso of first four pages:
        TL [copy], Inland Revenue. H.M. Inspector of Taxes to Messrs. Smith and Earle, January 23, 1928
      - AM & TM [notes on Howell and the Dukes of Cleveland, with an article on the Dukes of Cleveland] (continued) -- 1928 (Box 15, Folder 11-a-w)
        TLS, Smith and Earle to Violet Hunt, January 26, 1928
        TL [copy], Chase, Henderson and Tennant to Smith and Earle, June 13, 1928
        TLS, Smith and Earle to Violet Hunt, June 13, 1928.
        On verso of other notes are fragments of a typescript version of The Wife of Rossetti and possibly The Flurried Years.
      - TM & AM [Howell Papers. Extracts. Communications from People.] -- [n.d.], 1888-1924 (Box 15, Folder 12-a-kk)
        [1920's]
        116 ll. + 1
        With typed copies of the following letters:
        Emma Summers Gill to Violet Hunt, March 12, 1923
        Emma Summers Gill to Violet Hunt, March 22, 1923
        Emma Summers Gill to Violet Hunt, March 7, 1923
        Frances Kate Howell to Emmie [Gill], Tuesday
        Frances Kate Howell to Emmie [Gill], December 31, 1887
        Charles A. Howell to Em[ma Gill], June 22, 1888
        M.H. Spielmann to Violet Hunt, October 30, 1922
        M.H. Spielmann to Violet Hunt, January 8, 1923
        M.H. Spielmann to Violet Hunt, February 1, 1923
        George C. Williamson to Violet Hunt, April 14, 1924
        Mary F. Alleyne Clark to Violet Hunt, March 9, 1923
        Mary F. Alleyne Clark to Violet Hunt, [extract], March 13, 1923
      - TM & AM [Howell Papers. Extracts. Communications from People.] (continued) -- [n.d.], 1888-1924 (Box 15, Folder 12-a-kk)
        Phoebe Allen to Violet Hunt, [n.d.]
        R.H.A. [Richard Heron Allen] to Violet Hunt, March 19, 1923
        Annie L.C. Corfield to Charlotte Corder, [frag.], [n.d.]
        Alan S. Cole to Violet Hunt, January 9, 1923
        William Michael Rossetti to Charles A. Howell, June 15, 1882
        George C. Williamson to Violet Hunt, March 12, 1923.
        Cornell has the originals to some of these letters.
      - TM & AM [Howell Papers. Extracts. Communications from People.] (continued) -- [n.d.], 1888-1924 (Box 15, Folder 12-a-kk)
        Original letters:
        TLS, Metropolitan District Railway Co. to Violet Hunt, March 13, 1923
        TLS, J. Johnston Abraham to Violet Hunt, March 24, 1924
        TLS, Henry Head to Violet Hunt, November 7, 1922.
        Other typed copies:
        Statement by Emma Summers Gill
        Byron Webber, "From the Memoirs of James C. Orrock"
        C.J. Feret, "From Fulham Old and New"; "From the Folklore of M.H. [Margaret Hunt]"
        Edward Heron Allen, "Notes on 'Danner'"
        Henry Doetsch, "Testimonial [for Charles A. Howell]," December 11, 1888
        G.C. Williamson, "From Murray Marks and His Friends"; "From Pall Mall Budget," May 8, 1890.
      - AM & TM [notes and letters concerning Howell] -- [n.d.], 1873-1879 (Box 16, Folder 1-a-gg, 2-a-cc, & 3-a-x)
        89 ll. + 76 + 50 + 1
        With original folder cover.
        Housed in three folders.
      - AM & TM [notes and letters concerning Howell] (continued) -- [n.d.], 1873-1879 (Box 16, Folder 1-a-gg, 2-a-cc, & 3-a-x)
        Algernon C. Swinburne to Charles A. Howell, February 6, 1873
        Algernon C. Swinburne to Charles A. Howell, [frag.], February 9, 1873
        Algernon C. Swinburne to Camden Hotten, [frag.], [n.d.]
        Charles A. Howell to D.G. Rossetti, December 13, 1875
        Charles A. Howell to Algernon C. Swinburne, October 3, 1877
        Algernon C. Swinburne to Charles A. Howell, October 8, 1877
        Charles A. Howell to Manager, Brompton Cemetery, April 22, 1879.
      - TM [copy] [excerpts from various diaries] -- [n.d.], 1867-1884 (Box 16, Folder 4a-mm & 5-a-ss)
        103 ll. + 107 + 1
        Mostly excerpts from the diaries of G.P. Boyce, William Allingham, and William Michael Rossetti, with comments by Violet Hunt.
        With TL [copy], Charles A. Howell to Algernon C. Swinburne, August 26, 1867, and TL [copy] Alfred W. Hunt to Margaret Raine Hunt, [n.d.].
        With typed sheet containing Hunt family accounts for January-October, 1884.
        Some excerpts are on the verso of other unidentified manuscripts.
      - TM & AM [notes on Charles Augustus Howell] -- [1920s] (Box 16 & 17, Folder 6-a-q & 1-a-o)
        110 ll. + 70 ll.
        Many notes typed on the verso of a typescript of Violet Hunt's The Wife of Rossetti, though others are on the verso of unidentified manuscripts.
        TL from E.F. Richards to Violet Hunt, September 10, 1927. Notes on reverse
      - TM Howell biography (Charles Augustus) - Part V (2) - Second typing -- [n.d.] (Box 17, Folder 2-a-f)
        264 ll. + 1
        With cover.
    - c. Siddal Biography Papers
      - TM & AM [notes on Elizabeth Siddal] -- 1854--1913 (Box 17, Folder 3-a-v & 4-a-w)
        1865
        In two folders.
        With excerpts from William Allingham's diary.
        With page from Violet Hunt's diary at the beginning of the second folder.
        With brief genealogy of Elizabeth Siddal Rossetti.
        With the following letters:
        TL (copy) from John Ruskin to D. G. Rossetti, October ?, 1855
        TL (copy) from Elizabeth Siddal Rossetti to D. G. Rossetti, Christmas time 1855
        TL (copy) from Levin Schucking to Ford Madox Ford, Dec. 29, 1913
        TL (copy, frag.) from [D.G. Rossetti] to [Ford Madox Brown?], [n.d.]
        TL (copy) from Ford Madox Brown to Francis Hueffer, Sept. 9, 1871.
        With the following poems:
        "Early Death" (DGR-ESR)
        "The Passing of Love" (DGR-ESR)
        "A Year and a Day " (EES)
        "A Silent Wood" (DGR-ESR)
        "Hopeless Love" (Ford Madox Brown [?])
        "Broken Love" (William Blake)
        "What transgressions I commit" (unidentified)
        "He and She and Angels Three" (DGR-ESR).
      - TM & AM [notes on Elizabeth Siddal] (continued) -- 1854--1913 (Box 17, Folder 3-a-v & 4-a-w)
        On verso of some sheets is unidentified typed manuscript material. On verso of one sheet is TL [frag., draft], [n.d.], by Violet Hunt to [?], discussing Ford Madox Ford's defense of James Joyce's novel Ulysses.
      - Rossetti-Siddal family. -- [1932] (Box 17, Folder 5)
        M [printed] [genealogy]
        With Elizabeth Siddal Rossetti's genealogy on a separate page.
        Proof sheets for both genealogies. The proof sheets differ from the printed versions found in Violet Hunt's biography of Elizabeth Siddal Rossetti, The Wife of Rossetti.
  - 2. By others (by author)
    - Rossetti, Dante Gabriel, 1828-1882. -- Mar. 30, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      AD [copy] Certificate of Marriage
      Of his marriage to Elizabeth Siddal.
      With envelope with notes in Violet's hand.
    - Freemantle, W. T. -- [Aug. 29, 1928] (Box 17, Folder 7)
      AM [genealogy of Elizabeth Siddal]
      With another brief genealogy of Elizabeth Siddal Rossetti by a Miss Higgins, addressed to W. T. Freemantle.
    - Cochran, Charles Blake, Sir, 1872?-1951. -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 10-a-c)
      AM [copy] & [printed] [fragment of an article about Charles Blake Cochran]
      With a handwritten copy of some parts of the article and with the printed version of other parts, clipped, as it appears, from the original.
      Published in The Sketch.
    - Ford, Ford Madox, 1873-1939. -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 11)
      AM [notes for a lecture to troops]
      8 ll.
      With diagrams.
    - [Ford, Ford Madox, 1873-1939?] -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 12)
      TM [frag.] Zummurud
      38 ll.
      Playscript.
    - AMS "Tempo Rubato" -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Scott, William Bell, 1811-1890. -- [Feb. 27, 1882] (Box 18, Folder 14)
      AMS [init.] "At Sea" and "The Hurricane"
      With envelope addressed to Violet Hunt.
      Attributed to Studies from Nature.
    - Unidentified [Ford Madox Ford?] -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 15-a)
      AM "Bacchus Abroad"
    - Unidentified [Ford Madox Ford?] -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 15-b)
      AM "Fragment of a Tragedy"
      Written in pencil.
    - Unidentified [? Griffith?] -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 15-c)
      AM Poem: From the studio named the Cockloft/ Comes this message penned by Griffith,
      60, Fitzjohn's Avenue, N.W.
    - Unidentified -- Mar. 24, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 15-d)
      AM Recipe for sponge cake sent to Violet Hunt
      With two enclosures and envelope.
    - Unidentified [Lord Fermanagh?] -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 16)
      AM part of rental agreement for Rantisward Marsh
      Porridge house?
    - poem fragment, Ford Madox Brown 1p. -- [n.d.] (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - "Riesenberg" by Ford Madox Hueffer -- 1931 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Series V. Documents - Miscellaneous Documents, By Individual
  - Bathoe, William -- Apr. 17, 1750 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    ADS [receipt]
  - Ford, Ford Madox, 1873-1939. -- 1911 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    ADS [Coronation of King George V and Queen Mary] -- [press ticket]
  - Ford, Ford Madox, 1873-1939. -- [1913] (Box 18, Folder 3)
    TD [legal deposition concerning Ford's relationship with his wife Elsie]
    Unsigned.
  - Freer, Emily -- [1870] (Box 18, Folder 4-a)
    D [printed] funeral card
  - Freer, Louisa -- [1876] (Box 18, Folder 4-b)
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- Oct. 19, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    TD [birth certificate] -- [copy]
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- Aug. 6, 1879 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    AD [school certificate]
    Second Grade Certificate in model drawing awarded by the Science and Art Department of the Committee of Council on Education.
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- July 20, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    AD Society for the Protection of Birds -- [membership card]
  - Royal Academy of Arts (London) -- May 3, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    D [printed] [seating list and chart for annual dinner]
  - Scarborough Hospital and Dispensary Ball -- Jan. 3, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    D [printed] [program]
    Unlikely that it is Violet Hunt's copy -- records female dance partners.
  - "Novels by Violet Hunt" -- [n.d.] (Box 25, Folder 14)
    publisher's promotional pamphlet
    10 copies
  - Death Certificate -- Mar. 28, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Charles Siddall
  - Death Certificate -- Mar. 29, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Elizabeth Eleanor Siddall
  - Visiting Card: D.G. Rossetti -- [n.d.] (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - John Ruskin Printed Items, some autograph -- 1860 1886 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - John Ruskin clippings -- 1864-1882, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - 4 postcards -- 1931, 1936, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Photographs -- 1862-1863, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 17)
    Photographs of: G.P. Boyce,
    Oliver Madox Brown,
    "Mrs. Madox Brown as Cinderella (sketch),"
    Lady Burne-Jones "Georgina" & son Philip [2 c.],
    Thomas Carlyle,
    Sarah Cox "Fanny"
  - George Cruikshank, -- 1866, 1868, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Walter Howell Deverell "by Holman Hunt," Emperor & Empress of the French (Nap & Eugenie),
    Miss Herbert,
    D. D. Home,
    J.C. Hooke,
    W. Holman Hunt,
    H. S. Mendelssohn (W. B. Scott)
  - J. E. Millais, -- 1873, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    Mrs. Millais,
    William Morris,
    Mrs. Rae's "Fanny" (painting),
    John Ruskin (early and later)
  - Christina Rossetti, -- 1827, 1863 [?], 1867 [?], 1879, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    D. G. Rossetti (3),
    caricature of D. G. Rossetti (2 c.),
    W. Rossetti
  - Charles Crookes Siddall, -- n.d. (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Miss Siddall (3 c.),
    Elizabeth Eleanor Siddall (3 sketches - 2 c. of 2)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Tebbs, -- 1866, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 22)
    Margaret Webster,
    Augusta Wells,
    N.J Woolmer
  - Unidentified woman [Christina Rossetti?], envelope -- [n.d.] (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Series VI. Miscellaneous
  - Ford Madox Brown -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Hair clipping
    In envelope marked "Hair of FMB"
  - Louie -- Oct. 21, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    In envelope.
  - Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942. -- [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Button
    In envelope marked "IVH button".
  - Calendar -- 1939 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Hunt, Violet -- [1880] (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Address book
- Series VII. Photographs
  - [Cards and Envelopes] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 1-a-f)
    AM
    3 ll. + 3 envelopes
    Envelopes and cards with notes by Violet Hunt.
  - [MaNenet] -- Oct. 17, [1910?] and [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 2-a-b)
    2 AL [photographic copy] S to Henry Reymond
    Photograph of both letters and envelopes.
  - [Unidentified actor in theatrical pose] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Photograph
  - [Three unidentified men] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 4, 5, & 6)
    Three portrait photographs
    All three photographs were taken at The Biograph Studio at 107 Regent St., W., [London].
  - [Photograph album? - loose sheets] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Eight photographs
    Eight photographs attached to loose sheets of paper, possibly part of a larger album. Two of the photographs appear to be of Violet Hunt's niece, Rosamund Fogg-Elliot Wilkinson, one photograph is of two young sisters, two photographs appear to be of Canon William Greenwell, Violet Hunt's godfather, two photographs are of unidentified women in different poses, Viva Sherman at Bolam Lake, Whalton.
  - [Two unidentified women] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 8 & 9)
    Two portrait photographs
    Possibly the same woman. In both photographs the woman is wearing a hat.
  - [Unidentified woman] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Taken by C.N. Wootton, Cheltenham and originally enclosed with Maude La Fevriere, ALS to Miss Dodd, November 11 [1925].
  - [Group of women] -- June 16, 1877 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    According to a note written by Violet Hunt on the verso, "Papa [Alfred Hunt] met [the women] in Norway." Various names, all different, and Soque Fiord also are written on the back, though in a different hand than Violet's.
  - [Two unidentified women and dog in rowboat] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 12)
    In two pieces.
  - [Four unidentified individuals] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 13, 14, 15, & 16)
    Four portrait photographs
    Three women and one man. One photograph a photograph postcard. The other three were done at the following studios: T.H. Larmuth, Turnbridge Wells; J. Perriman, Camden Town, London, N.W.; Clement Rogers, Derby.
  - [Monk, Lady Nani?] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 17)
    On verso Violet Hunt has written "Mrs Reed's old/ house in/ Clarges 81/ (Claridges a/blacksmith. (Lady/ [Nani Monk?].)"
  - Bamburgh Castle -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Photograph of manuscript page with drawing of Bamburgh Castle after the seige
    With note in Violet Hunt's handwriting on separate sheet of paper.
  - Hulme-Beaman, Ardern G. (Ardern George), 1857-1929. -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Mounted on card that reads Army and Navy Aux'ry, C.S.Ld, Francis Street, Westminster S.W.
    With inscription, in Arabic characters, and signature on verso.
  - Benson, Constance -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 20)
    By Guy & Co., Cork.
    Inscribed and signed.
  - Benson, Sir Frank Robert, 1858-1939. -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 21 & 22)
    Two photographs
    Both inscribed and signed.
    Both show Benson in costume, as Hamlet and [Julius Caesar?].
    One by Elliott & Fry [London], the other by A. Bassano [London].
  - Benson, William -- [1886?] (Box 19, Folder 23)
    By Kingsbury & Notcutt, London.
  - Bernhardt, Sarah, 1844-1923. -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Cut out of magazines? and pasted on cards.
  - Boyce, Violet Annan -- Jan. 1900 and [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 25 & 26)
    Dated photograph by H.& R. Stiles [London].
    Undated photograph shows Mrs. Boyce in Middle Eastern garb, and note on card to which the photograph is attached indicates it was taken in Baghdad.
  - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Browning, Robert, 1812-1889. -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 28)
    Two copies of the same photograph.
  - [Burne-Jones child?] -- [Nov. 16, 1866?] (Box 19, Folder 29)
    Photograph of child praying
    With notes about identity of child [Georgina B.-J.?] on verso of photograph and on envelope in which the photograph was housed.
    By J.R. James, Islington.
  - Burne-Jones, Georgiana, Lady, 1840-1920. -- Aug. 7, 1862 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Photograph of Mrs. Burne-Jones holding her infant son Philip
    By W. Jeffrey [London].
  - Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, Sir, 1833-1898. -- Oct. 7, 1867 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    Photograph of painting by [Burne-Jones?]
    With note on verso stating that Edwd. Burne-Jones gave this to G.P. Boyce.
  - Carrie's grandparents -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 32)
    By Drewett, Guildford.
  - Chalon, H. G. -- [1930s] (Box 19, Folder 33)
    Photograph of "Raby Kennel, 1820" a painting by Chalon
    Howell materials.
  - [Child, Annie?] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 34)
    By Newton & Co., East Molesey and Teddington.
  - Coghill, Mr. and Mrs. A.C. -- Aug. 7, 1926 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Collins, Lottie -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 36)
    Photograph of Collins in "Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay"
    Theater photograph by the London Stereoscopic Corp.
  - [Conrad family] -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 37)
    Group photograph
    Joseph Conrad's family?
    Three women, three men, and a dog.
  - Conrad, Joseph, 1857-1924. -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Corder, Rosa -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 39)
    Photograph of Rosa Corder with her hair down
  - Corder, Rosa -- [n.d.] (Box 19, Folder 40)
    Photograph of oil painting of Rosa Corder